<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Top 20 programming languages</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Top 20 programming languages</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 22:52:53 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Top 20 Programming Languages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 22:52:53 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/list/</guid>
      <description>List Name Description Logo Python Python is a versatile and powerful language that lets you work quickly and integrate systems more effectively. Learn more about Python, download the latest version, read the documentation, find jobs, and join the community. C This tutorial covers all the basic to advanced concepts of C programming language, such as variables, arrays, pointers, strings, loops, functions, etc. It is designed for both beginners and experienced professionals who want to learn and enhance their knowledge of C programming language.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/assemblylanguage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/assemblylanguage/</guid>
      <description>Assembly language Programming Language Programming in assembly for PCs though is a little tricky. A lot of information about PC assembly language dates back from when assembly was more common, but it also covers old modes that &amp;hellip;&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/c</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/c</guid>
      <description>C# Programming Language A new report promotes preventing cyberattacks by using memory-safe languages, and the development of software safety standards.&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/c&#43;&#43;/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/c&#43;&#43;/</guid>
      <description>C++ Programming Language Shifting toward memory-safe programming languages could alleviate cybersecurity risks for individuals and small businesses, the Biden administration claims.&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/c/</guid>
      <description>C Programming Language A new report promotes preventing cyberattacks by using memory-safe languages, and the development of software safety standards.&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/cobol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/cobol/</guid>
      <description>COBOL Programming Language Many have systems that still rely on Cobol, a programming language first released in the early 1960s, as part of a program sponsored by the U.S. Department of Defense. &amp;ldquo;Banking systems are loaded with Cobol, it was built ages ago, it&amp;rsquo;s not documented &amp;hellip;&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/delphiobjectpascal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/delphiobjectpascal/</guid>
      <description>Delphi/Object Pascal Programming Language A new report promotes preventing cyberattacks by using memory-safe languages, and the development of software safety standards.&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/fortran/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/fortran/</guid>
      <description>Fortran Programming Language The White House Office of the National Cyber Director (ONCD) urged tech companies today to switch to memory-safe programming languages, such as Rust, to improve software security by reducing the number of memory safety vulnerabilities.&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/go/</guid>
      <description>Go Programming Language A new report promotes preventing cyberattacks by using memory-safe languages, and the development of software safety standards.&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/java/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/java/</guid>
      <description>Java Programming Language Project Leyden is also within the scope of turning Java into a perfect programming language for cloud-native apps. The project&amp;rsquo;s primary goal is to &amp;ldquo;improve the startup time, time to peak performance and footprint of Java programs.&amp;rdquo; Among the expected &amp;hellip;&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/javascript/</guid>
      <description>JavaScript Programming Language When Fridman says JavaScript runs the world, in other words, what he means is that our world is, like the underlying source code, massively screwed up and incomprehensible. It&amp;rsquo;s the equivalent of pronouncing, with a sigh, that considering the sorry state of the planet, the Universal Declaration of Human Rights must have been written in Comic Sans.&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/kotlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/kotlin/</guid>
      <description>Kotlin Programming Language Value stream management involves people in the organization to examine workflows and other processes to ensure they are deriving the maximum value from their efforts while eliminating waste — of &amp;hellip;&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/matlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/matlab/</guid>
      <description>MATLAB Programming Language The focus is on computer programming in general, but the numerous language features that make MATLAB uniquely suited to engineering and scientific computing are also covered in depth. Topics &amp;hellip;&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/php/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/php/</guid>
      <description>PHP Programming Language PHP is one of the most used programming languages. How has it remained on top and what are some of the pros and cons for developers?&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/python/</guid>
      <description>Python Programming Language Getty Images Trends for Stack Overflow reveal that Python-related inquiries dominate the platform, accounting for approximately 13% of all questions posted in its Q&amp;amp;A forums. Insights show that on Stack Overflow, the programming language has consistently &amp;hellip;&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/ruby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/ruby/</guid>
      <description>Ruby Programming Language The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) will start providing more hands-on support to open-source software developers as they work to better secure their projects, the agency first told Axios.&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/rust/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/rust/</guid>
      <description>Rust Programming Language A new report promotes preventing cyberattacks by using memory-safe languages, and the development of software safety standards.&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/scratch/</guid>
      <description>Scratch Programming Language Scratch is a block-based programming language designed for elementary school children, letting them learn fundamental concepts while experimenting in an environment filled with visual and audible &amp;hellip;&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/sql/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/sql/</guid>
      <description>SQL Programming Language &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s the very first study to demonstrate that vulnerabilities of large language models in general &amp;hellip; can translate human questions into the SQL programming language, which is commonly used &amp;hellip;&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/swift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/swift/</guid>
      <description>Swift Programming Language Apple has released Swift 5.10, an update to the company&amp;rsquo;s open-source programming language that reaches a major milestone: providing safety against data races via full data isolation in the concurrency model. The improvement prepares the way for the &amp;hellip;&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>subpage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/visualbasic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/langs/visualbasic/</guid>
      <description>Visual Basic Programming Language Visual Basic 6.0 is a user-friendly programming language by Microsoft notable for its simplicity and effectiveness in developing Windows applications. Designed with an easy-to-learn approach &amp;hellip;&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
